(Raj:)...mixer for grad students
and faculty...
(Raj:)...of the Science
and Humanities Departments.
(Raj:)Whether you split atoms or infinitives,
this is the place to be."
(Sheldon:)Well, that's certainly amusing...
(Sheldon:)...but I have no interest.
(Raj:)Come on, Sheldon.
(Raj:)The world is filled with people
doing things outside.
(Raj:)Let's go outside. Outside is good.
(Sheldon:)If outside is so good...
(Sheldon:)...why has mankind spent thousands
of years trying to perfect inside?
(Raj:)I don't know. It's a marketing scheme.
(Raj:)Please, Sheldon, I'm a young,
virile visitor from a foreign land...
(Raj:)...and I need to strut my stuff.
(Sheldon:)Let me offer you a compromise.
(Sheldon:)Sometimes when I feel stifled
and want a change of scenery...
(Sheldon:)...I use my imagination.
(Raj:)Oh, boy.
One of my favorite places to visit
is the two-dimensional world...
(Sheldon:)...described in Edwin Abbott's
mathematical fantasy Flatland.
I don't wanna go to Flatland.